The Guide to the John Canemaker Animation Collection 1903-2012 (Bulk 1970-2000) MSS 040
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I:Documentary Material
  - Subseries B: People
    - Canemaker, John: ROCKY HORRORSHOW commercial, undated (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Canemaker, John: SAFESEX, undated (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Canemaker, John: SEARCHING CA, ORKAZ VS. THEGYPSY MOTH, undated (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Canemaker,John: SILVER SCREEN PARTNERS IV, undated (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Canemaker, John: STREET FREAKS, undated (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Canemaker, John: UNIDENTIFIED FLYING PRANKSTERS, undated (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Canemaker, John: WHAT DO CHILDREN THINK OF WHENTHEYTHINK OF THE BOMB?, undated (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Canemaker, John: WHO'S THAT GIRL?, undated (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Canemaker, John: THEWIZARD'S SON, undated (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Canemaker, John: THEWIZARD'S SON, undated (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Canemaker, John: THE WORLD ACCORDING TO GARP, undated (Box 8, Folder 52-53)
    - Canemaker, John: YOU DON'T HAVE TO DIE, undated (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Caniff, Milton, undated (Box 17, Folder 188)
    - Catteneo, Tony ***see*** Wyatt, Ron, undated (Box 17)
    - Clampett, Bob, undated (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Cohl, Emile, undated (Box 8, Folder 56-58)
    - Cohl, Emile, undated (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Collins,Vincent, undated (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Cruikshank, Sally, undated (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Cruikshank, Sally, undated (Box 40, Folder 350)
    - Cuba, Larry, undated (Box 9, Folder 62.1)
    - Culhane,Shamus, undated (Box 9, Folder 62.2)
    - Culhane, Shamus, undated (Box 40, Folder 349)
    - David, Tissa-Films-RAGGEDY ANN &ANDY ***see*** Williams, Richard, undated (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - DeChomon, Segundo, undated (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Deitch, Gene, undated (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Deja, Adreas, undated (Box 16, Folder 171)
    - Diaz, Ron, undated (Box 16, Folder 171)
    - Disney,Walt: General, undated (Box 9, Folder 66-67)
    - Disney, Walt: Joe Grant Study Collection, undated (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Disney, Walt: ALADDIN, undated (Box 26, Folder 252)
    - Disney, Walt: ALICE INWONDERLAND, undated (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Disney, Walt: BEAUTY AND THE BEAST, undated (Box 26, Folder 250)
    - Disney, Walt: THEBLACK CAULDRON, undated (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Disney, Walt: DONQUIXOTE, undated (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - Disney, Walt:, Walt:DUMBO, undated (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - Disney, Walt: DUMBO WORKDRAFT, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 231)
    - Disney, Walt:FANTASIA, undated (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Disney, Walt: FANTASIA, undated (Box 27, Folder 261)
    - Disney, Walt: FANTASIA, undated (Box 28, Folder 262-265)
    - Disney, Walt:THE FOX AND THE HOUND, undated (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - Disney, Walt: THE JUNGLE BOOK, undated (Box 10, Folder 75-76)
    - Disney, Walt: THE JUNGLE BOOK WORKDRAFT, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 233)
    - Disney,Walt: THE LITTLE MERMAID, undated (Box 10, Folder 77.1)
    - Disney,Walt: MAKE MINE MUSIC, undated (Box 10, Folder 77.2)
    - Disney, Walt:MARY POPPINS, undated (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - Disney, Walt:MELODY TIME, undated (Box 10, Folder 79.1)
    - Disney, Walt: OLIVER& COMPANY, undated (Box 10, Folder 79.2)
    - Disney, Walt: 101 DALMATIONS, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 247)
    - Disney, Walt: PETERPAN, undated (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - Disney, Walt: PINOCCHIO, undated (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - Disney, Walt: PINNOCHIO WORKDRAFT, 1940 (Box 23, Folder 232)
    - Disney, Walt: RETURN TO OZ, undated (Box 10, Folder 82)
    - Disney, Walt: SNOW WHITE & THE SEVENDWARFS, undated (Box 10, Folder 83)
    - Disney, Walt:TRON, undated (Box 10, Folder 84)
    - Disney, Walt: Miscellaneous Features, undated (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - Disney, Walt: Miscellaneous Shorts, undated (Box 10, Folder 86)
    - Disney, Walt: Disney-MGM ThemePark, undated (Box 21, Folder 220-222)
    - Disney, Walt: Disney Animation Storyboarding, undated (Box 23, Folder 230)
    - Disney, Walt: Dissertation - Robin Allen, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 249)
    - Disney, Walt: Disney-Animation Guides, undated (Box 32, Folder 285)
    - Disney, Walt: Disney - Talent Devel. Discussion Group, undated (Box 32, Folder 290)
    - Disney, Walt: Disney - Articles, 1984-1995 (Box 32, Folder 297)
    - Disney, Walt: Disney - Articles, 1932-1996 (Box 37, Folder 323-324)
    - Disney, Walt: Disney - Articles, 1932-1996 (Box 38, Folder 325-331)
    - Disney, Walt: Disney - Articles, 1932-1996 (Box 39, Folder 338)
    - Disney, Walt: Disney - Articles, undated (Box 27, Folder 332)
    - Disney, Walt: Disney - Annual Report, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 340)
    - Disney, Walt: Disney - Correspondence, 1938-1955 (Box 39, Folder 341)
    - Disney, Walt: Disney - Student Paper: Disney and Gender, undated (Box 39, Folder 342)
    - Disney, Walt: Disney - Uncompleted Film List, undated (Box 39, Folder 343)
    - Disney, Walt: Disney - Disneyana Convention, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 364)
    - Disney, Walt: Disney - Analysis: M. Mouse, et al., undated (Box 41, Folder 366)
    - Dopff, Paul, undated (Box 10, Folder 87)
    - Drouin, Jacques, undated (Box 10, Folder 88)
    - Duesing, James, undated (Box 10, Folder 89)
    - Dunning, George, undated (Box 10, Folder 90)
    - Dunning, George, undated (Box 40, Folder 351)
    - Dyer, Anson, undated (Box 10, Folder 91)
    - Edera, Bruno, undated (Box 11, Folder 92)
    - Emes, Ian, undated (Box 11, Folder 93)
    - Engel, Jules, undated (Box 11, Folder 94)
    - Engel, Jules, undated (Box 40, Folder 358)
    - Enguster, Al, undated (Box 18, Folder 201)
    - Fawdry, Richard, undated (Box 11, Folder 95)
    - Fischinger, Oscar & Elfriede, undated (Box 11, Folder 96-97.1)
    - Fischinger, Oscar & Elfriede, undated (Box 33, Folder 298-301)
    - Fisher, Bud, undated (Box 11, Folder 97.2)
    - Fitzsimmons, John A., undated (Box 17, Folder 189)
    - Fleischer, Max & Dave, undated (Box 11, Folder 98-99)
    - Foray, June, undated (Box 11, Folder 100)
    - Freleng, Friz, undated (Box 11, Folder 101)
    - Gardiner, Bob ***see*** Vinton, Will, undated (Box 11, Folder 101)
    - Gilliam, Terry, undated (Box 12, Folder 102)
    - Godfrey, Bob, undated (Box 12, Folder 103)
    - Golden, Books, undated (Box 30, Folder 271)
    - Griffin, George, undated (Box 12, Folder 104)
    - Grillo, Oscar, undated (Box 12, Folder 105)
    - Gross, Anthony, undated (Box 12, Folder 106)
    - Gross, Anthony, undated (Box 40, Folder 360)
    - Hahn, Don, undated (Box 16, Folder 171)
    - Halas, John & Batchelor, Joy, undated (Box 12, Folder 107)
    - Halas, John & Batchelor, Joy, undated (Box 40, Folder 361)
    - Hall, David, undated (Box 30, Folder 276)
    - Hand, David, undated (Box 12, Folder 108)
    - Hawkins, Emery, undated (Box 12, Folder 109)
    - Hench, John, undated (Box 30, Folder 270)
    - Henson, Tex, undated (Box 12, Folder 110)
    - Holland, Sylvia, undated (Box 27, Folder 273)
    - Holland, Sylvia, undated (Box 30, Folder 274)
    - Horvath, Ferdinand, undated (Box 30, Folder 266-269)
    - Hubley, John & Faith, undated (Box 12, Folder 111)
    - Hubley, John & Faith, undated (Box 40, Folder 347)
    - Huemer, Richard, undated (Box 12, Folder 112-113)
    - Hult, Lars - Arne, undated (Box 12, Folder 114)
    - Hurter, Albert, undated (Box 30, Folder 272)
    - Jittlov, Mike, undated (Box 12, Folder 115)
    - Johnston, Ollie ***see*** Thomas, Frank, undated (Box 12)
    - Jones, Bob, undated (Box 30, Folder 277)
    - Jones, Chuck, undated (Box 12, Folder 116)
    - Jones, Chuck, undated (Box 31, Folder 278-283)
    - Jones, Chuck, undated (Box 27, Folder 284)
    - Kahl, Milt, undated (Box 12, Folder 117)
    - Katzenberg, Jeffrey, undated (Box 16, Folder 171)
    - Khitruk, Fedor, undated (Box 12, Folder 118)
    - Kijowicz, Miroslaw, undated (Box 12, Folder 119)
    - Kimball, Ward, undated (Box 12, Folder 120)
    - Kinney, Jack, undated (Box 12, Folder 121)
    - Klein, I., undated (Box 13, Folder 122)
    - Kopp,Harry, undated (Box 13, Folder 123)
    - Korty, John, undated (Box 13, Folder 124)
    - Lantz, Walter, undated (Box 13, Folder 125)
    - Lantz, Walter, undated (Box 40, Folder 362)
    - Leach, John & Rankin, Jean, undated (Box 13, Folder 126)
    - Leaf, Caroline &Soul, Veronika, undated (Box 13, Folder 127)
    - Leaf, Caroline, undated (Box 40, Folder 363)
    - Leigh, Douglas, undated (Box 26, Folder 253)
    - Leiva, Stephen Paul, undated (Box 32, Folder 291)
    - Levitow, Abe, undated (Box 32, Folder 287)
    - Lieberman, Jerry, undated (Box 13, Folder 128)
    - Lounsbery, John, undated (Box 13, Folder 129)
    - Lye, Len, undated (Box 13, Folder 130)
    - Lye, Len, undated (Box 40, Folder 359)
    - McCay,Winsor ***see*** Box 17, undated (Box 13)
    - McClaren,Norman, undated (Box 13, Folder 131)
    - McClaren,Norman, undated (Box 41, Folder 365)
    - Markewich, Arthur, undated (Box 18, Folder 202)
    - Messmer, Otto ***see*** Box 7, Folder 39:Canemaker, undated (Box 18, Folder 203-204)
    - John-Film-OttoMessmer & Felix the Cat], undated (Box 18, Folder 205)
    - Miller, J.J., undated (Box 13, Folder 133)
    - Moniz, Ray W., undated (Box 17, Folder 194)
    - Moritz, William, undated (Box 13, Folder 134)
    - Moritz, William, undated (Box 33, Folder 302-305)
    - Moritz, William, undated (Box 35, Folder 306)
    - Morrison, Tammy ***see*** Terry, Paul, undated (Box 35)
    - Moser, Frank ***see*** Terry, Paul, undated (Box 35)
    - Mouris, Frank & Caroline, undated (Box 13, Folder 135)
    - Natwick, Grim[***see also: Box 18, Folder 203: Interview re: Otto Messmer], undated (Box 13, Folder 136)
    - Natwick, Grim, undated (Box 28, Folder 260)
    - Nibbelink, Paul, undated (Box 13, Folder 137)
    - Nielsen, Kay, undated (Box 28, Folder 257)
    - Nordberg, Cliff, undated (Box 32, Folder 292)
    - Norstein, Yuri, undated (Box 14, Folder 138)
    - Noyes, Eliot, undated (Box 14, Folder 139)
    - O'Neill, Pat, undated (Box 14, Folder 140)
    - Oriolo, Joe ***see*** Oversize Box 20., undated (Box 18, Folder 204)
    - Padron, Juan, undated (Box 14, Folder 141)
    - Pal, George, undated (Box 14, Folder 142)
    - Park, Nick, undated (Box 20, Folder 246)
    - Parker, Claire ***see*** Alexeieff, Alexander, undated (Box 14)
    - Pies, Dennis, undated (Box 14, Folder 143)
    - Pies, Dennis, undated (Box 40, Folder 357)
    - Pitt, Suzan, undated (Box 14, Folder 144)
    - Plympton, Bill, undated (Box 40, Folder 353)
    - Potterton, Gerald, undated (Box 14, Folder 145)
    - Protovin, Richard, undated (Box 14, Folder 146)
    - Protovin, Richard, undated (Box 40, Folder 354)
    - Rankin, Arthur Jr. &Bass, Jules, undated (Box 14, Folder 147)
    - Rankin, Jean ***see*** Leach, John, undated (Box 14)
    - Reiniger, Lotte, undated (Box 14, Folder 148)
    - Ren & Stimpy, undated (Box 27, Folder 254)
    - Richter, Hans, undated (Box 14, Folder 149)
    - Ring, Borge, undated (Box 14, Folder 150)
    - Rose, Kathy, undated (Box 14, Folder 151)
    - Rose, Kathy, undated (Box 28, Folder 258)
    - Rybczynski, Zbigniew, undated (Box 40, Folder 355)
    - Leon Schlesinger Productions, undated (Box 32, Folder 288)
    - Schneider, Peter, undated (Box 16, Folder 171)
    - Schwartz, Lillian, undated (Box 14, Folder 152)
    - Sito, Thomas R., undated (Box 14, Folder 153)
    - Solomon, Charles, undated (Box 16, Folder 172)
    - Soul, Veronika ***see*** Leaf, Caroline, undated (Box 16)
    - Spafford, Dave, undated (Box 16, Folder 171)
    - Sporn, Michael, undated (Box 14, Folder 154)
    - Stapp, Philip, undated (Box 14, Folder 155)
    - Sullivan, Pat***see*** Oversize Box 20, undated (Box 18, Folder 208-208a)
    - Svankmajer, Jan, undated (Box 40, Folder 356)
    - Swathe, Robert, undated (Box 14, Folder 156)
    - Tenggren, Gustaf, undated (Box 35, Folder 307)
    - Terry, Paul, undated (Box 24, Folder 234-242)
    - Thomas, Frank & Johnston, Ollie, undated (Box 14, Folder 157-158)
    - Thomas, Frank & Johnston,Ollie-Films-Nemo, undated (Box 15, Folder 159)
    - Tytla, William, undated (Box 15, Folder 160-161)
    - Tytla, William, undated (Box 21, Folder 227-228)
    - Tytla, William, undated (Box 23, Folder 229)
    - Unidentified Animation Notes, undated (Box 32, Folder 296)
    - Vinton, Will & Gardiner, Bob, undated (Box 15, Folder 162)
    - Vujanovic, Branko & Zdenka, undated (Box 15, Folder 163)
    - Vukotic, Dusan, undated (Box 15, Folder 164)
    - Walker, Hal, undated (Box 18, Folder 209)
    - Ward, Jay, undated (Box 15, Folder 165)
    - Washom, Ben, undated (Box 32, Folder 286)
    - Weiss, William ***see*** Terry, Paul, undated (Box 32)
    - Whitney, James, undated (Box 15, Folder 166)
    - Whitney, John Sr., undated (Box 15, Folder 167)
    - Williams, Richard-General, undated (Box 16, Folder 168)
    - Williams,Richard-Films-RAGGEDY ANN & ANDY, undated (Box 16, Folder 169)
    - Williams, Richard-Films-WHO FRAMED ROGER RABBIT?, undated (Box 16, Folder 170-172)
    - Winkler, Margaret, undated (Box 16, Folder 173)
    - Wong, Ty, undated (Box 28, Folder 256)
    - Wyatt, Ron & Catteneo, Tony, undated (Box 16, Folder 174)
    - Canemaker, John- Books-WINSOR MCCAY, undated (Box 17)
    - Winsor McCay: Diary, 1908 (Box 17, Folder 180)
    - Winsor McCay: Article: Animated Art., undated (Box 17, Folder 181)
    - Winsor McCay: Article: How I Originated MotionPicture Cartoons., undated (Box 17, Folder 182)
    - Winsor McCay: Art: Gertie the Dynosaur: (copy), undated (Box 17, Folder 183-185)
    - Winsor McCay: Contracts, undated (Box 17, Folder 186)
    - Winsor McCay: Correspondence to W.M., 1903-1955 (Box 17, Folder 187)
    - Winsor McCay: Correspondence: Milton Caniff, undated (Box 17, Folder 188)
    - Winsor McCay: Typescript: "My Dayswith Winsor McCay," by John A. Fitzsimmons., undated (Box 17, Folder 189)
    - Winsor McCay: Newsclips, undated (Box 17, Folder 190-193)
    - Winsor McCay: Family History, undated (Box 17, Folder 194)
    - WinsorMcCay: Toys, etc. based ON W.M. Drawings, undated (Box 17, Folder 195)
    - Winsor McCay: John Canemaker's Book Proposal & Articles on W.M., undated (Box 17, Folder 196-197)
    - Winsor McCay: W.M.: Little Nemo's Daddy - Unpublished Biography by Padric O'Glasain, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 243-244)
    - Winsor McCay: Art of W.M. - PhD Diss., 1976 (Box 25, Folder 245)
    - Canemaker, John-Books-FELIX, undated (Box 18)
    - Computer discs (Felix the Cat), undated (Box 18, Folder 200)
    - Interviews: Al Eugaster, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 201)
    - Interviews: Arthur Markewich, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 202)
    - Interviews: Otto Messner, 1975-1980 (Box 18, Folder 203-204)
    - Interviews, Diary, 1918-1919 (Box 18, Folder 205)
    - Interviews: GrimNatwick, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 206)
    - Interviews: Joe Oriolo, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 207)
    - Interviews: Sullivant, Pat, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 208-208a)
    - Interviews: Hal Walker, 1978,1989 (Box 18, Folder 209)
    - Felix the Cat: Research Materials, undated (Box 19, Folder 210-213)
    - Book Typescript, undated (Box 19, Folder 214-215)
    - Book Galleys, undated (Box 19, Folder 216)
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 20, Folder 217-221)
    - Oversize DocumentaryMaterials, undated (Box 21)
    - Disney - MGMTheme Park, undated (Box 22, Folder 222-224)
- Series II: Graphic Material
  - Subseries A: Animators' Artwork
    Unless otherwise noted, Series II-A are in oversize boxes
    - Babbitt, Art, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Canemaker, John - Films - BOTTOM'S DREAM, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Canemaker,John - Films - CHILDREN'S TELEVISION WORKSHOP-DNA CONCERTO, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Canemaker: CHILDREN'S TELEVISIONWORKSHOP-SHAPE OF MATH, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Canemaker,John: CONFESSIONS OF A STARDREAMER, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - [framed on wall]Canemaker, John: CONFESSIONS OF A STARDREAMER, undated
    - Canemaker, John: COUNT ON KOTEX commercial, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Canemaker, John: THE 40'S, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Canemaker, John: GREED, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Canemaker, John: THE HUNGER PROJECT, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Canemaker, John: JOHN LENNON SKETCHBOOK, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Canemaker, John: LATE FOR DINNER, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Canemaker, John: LAUGHTER IS GOOD MEDICINE, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Canemaker, John: NEMO DREAMSEQUENCE, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Canemaker, John: RISINGSTAR VIDEO logo, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Canemaker, John: SEARCHING CA, OR KAZ VS. THEGYPSY MOTH, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Canemaker, John: SILVER SCREEN PARTNERS IV, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Canemaker, John-Films-STREET FREAKS, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Canemaker, John: WHAT DOCHILDREN THINK WHENTHEY THINK OF THE BOMB?, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Canemaker, John: WHO'S THAT GIRL?, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Canemaker, John: THE WIZARD'S SON, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - [map case]Canemaker, John: THE WIZARD'S SON, undated
    - Canemaker, John: THE WORLD ACCORDING TOGARP, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - [map case]Canemaker, John: THEWORLD ACCORDING TO GARP, undated
    - Canemaker,John: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - David, Tissa, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - David, Tissa-Films-RAGGEDY ANN & ANDY***see*** Williams, Richard, undated
    - Disney,Walt-Books-Treasures OF Disney Animation, undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Disney, Walt-Films-DON QUIXOTE, undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Disney,Walt-Films-JOHNNY APPLESEED, undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Disney,Walt-Films-MAKE MINE MUSIC, undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Disney,Walt-Films-MELODY TIME-BUMBLE BOOGIEsequence, undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Disney, Walt-Films-ONCE UPON A WINTERTIM Esequence, undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Disney, Walt-Films-PETER PAN, undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - [map case]Disney,Walt-Films-PINOCCHIO, undated
    - Disney,Walt-Films-SNOW WHITE & THE SEVENDWARFS, undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - [map case]Disney, Walt-Films-30 20" x 40" photostats, undated
    - Disney, Walt: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Dunbar, Geoff-Films-UBU, undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Fischinger, Oskar, undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Fleischer, Max &Dave, undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Freleng, Friz, undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Jones, Chuck, undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Klein, I., undated (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Petty, Sara, undated (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Ring, Borge, undated (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Sporn,Michael, undated (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Thomas, Frank & Johnston, Ollie:'-Books-Too Funny FOR Words, undated (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Tytla,William, undated (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Williams, Richard-Films-RAGGEDYANN & ANDY, undated (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Subseries C: Flip Books
    - Boxed set of 6 Flip Bookswith Brochure (Tony Eastman,Paul Glabicki, George Griffen, Roger Kukes, Sara Petty, KathyRose) Flames-Woman of the Year Rotoscope- Katonah Gallery Instruction Book The IncredibleMagic of Magic-Dance Lesson-Yves Brangolo Calarts-John Canemaker (2)-Ottawa '78(2)-Crayonite, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Emile Cohl (2)-ShamusCulhane-John Dilworth, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Walt Disney "FlipBook" from the Art Corner (3), undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Walt DisneyMoving Picture Flip Book (4), undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Paul Dopff (4), undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Paul Driessen (2)-James Duesing &Thomas Lenden-Oskar Fischinger, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - PeterFoldes-Harold Friedman-John & Faith Hubley (3), undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Jill & Al Jarnow-Miroslaw Kijowicz-Yoji Kuri-Vladimir Lehky, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Jan Lenica-Otto Messmer (2), undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Marv Newland (3)-Sandy, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Gary Schwartz-B. Shackman-SHR Communications-Richard Williams, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
- SeriesIII: Book Collection
  The book collection is housed in the Fales Library. The books have been catalogued in Bobcat. A keyword or related name search with the name Canemaker will retrieve the records for the books.
- Series IV: Periodical Collection
  These items are housed in the Fales Library. A list of the periodicals is available in the Reading Room.
- Series V: Audio & Video Tape Collection.
  Both the audio and videotape materials were originally housed in the Avery Fisher Center for Music and Media. In 2003, the audiotapes were transferred to the Fales Library and Special Collections. The videotapes remain in the Avery Fisher Center. Following is a list of the audiotapes.
  - Subseries A: Access Copies
    - J.R. Bray interview by John Canemaker; Bridgeport, CT.; March 25, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 40.0001)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
      Audiocassette, Maxell XLII 60
    - Art Babbitt remembers Bill Tytla in Los Angeles, March 1975 (Box 1, Folder 40.0002)
      Audiocassette, Maxell XLII 90
    - Art Babbitt interview by John Canemaker, New York City, June 4, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 40.0003)
    - Art Babbitt interview by John Canemaker, New York City., 1975 (Box 1, Folder 40.0004)
    - Side A: Ollie Johnston and Les Clark interviews, Disney Studio, Burbank, CA, July 5, 1973; Side B: Frank Thomas, Disney Studio, July 6, 1973. (Box 1, Folder 40.0005)
    - Otto Messmer, Fort Lee, NJ, March 5, 1975. (Box 1, Folder 40.0006)
    - John A Fitzsimmons (Winsor McCay's assistant), Rockville Center, NY, September 22, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 40.0007)
    - Side A: Otto Messmer, March 5, 1975; Side B: George Bakes on Bill Tytla, NYC, March 11, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 40.0008)
    - Shamus Culhane, NYC, February 13, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 40.0009)
    - Shamus Culhane, NYC, February 13, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 40.001)
    - Terri Gilliam (backstage City Center Theater), NYC, April 30, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 40.0011)
    - Emery Hawkins, NYC, January 12, 1976. (Box 1, Folder 40.0012)
    - Otto Messmer (final interview, talks about early life, etc.), January 29, 1979. (Box 1, Folder 40.0013)
    - Tex Hensen "remembers Walt Disney and Studio". Recorded in Dallas, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 40.0014)
    - Bruno Bozzetto, NYC, February 12, 1979., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 40.0015)
    - George Dunning, Ottowa, Canada, Sept. 1, 1978. (Box 1, Folder 40.0016)
    - Side A: Don Duckwall; Side B: Eric Larson, Heidi Guedel, Emily Guliano, Walt Disney Studio, Burbank, CA, April 25, 1978. (Box 1, Folder 40.0017)
    - Len Lye, NYC, interviewed by Joseph Kennedy and John Canemaker, August 22, 1976. (Box 1, Folder 40.0018)
    - Side A: Len Lye, NYC; Side B: Walter Lantz, June 16, 1977. (Box 1, Folder 40.0019)
    - Side A: Confessions of a Star Dreamer audio mix; Side B: Walter Lanz, June 16, 1977. (Box 1, Folder 40.002)
    - Richard Williams, NYC, July 18, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 40.0021)
    - Side A: Richard Williams, NYC; Side B: Joe Raposo (on Raggedy Ann and Andy), July 19, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 40.0022)
    - Side A: David R. Smith, Disney Archives, Burbank, CA; Disney animation trainees, July 6, 1973; Side B: Ward Kimball, Arcadia, CA, July 7, 1973. (Box 1, Folder 40.0023)
    - Ward Kimball, Arcadia, CA, July 7, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 40.0024)
    - Harold Walker on Pat Sullivan, Otto Messmer, and Felix the Cat, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 40.0025)
    - Art Babbitt on Don Graham and Disney art school, February 21, 1979. (Box 1, Folder 40.0026)
    - Frank Thomas answers list of questions, September 9, 1974. (Box 1, Folder 40.0027)
    - Grim Natwick, NYC, May 19, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 40.0028)
    - Richard Williams on Raggedy Ann and Andy, NYC, December 2, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 40.0029)
    - Elfriede Fischinger and William Moritz interviewed by P. Adams Sitney on ArtForum, May 6, 1977., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 40.003)
    - George Griffin, NYC, September 5, 1985. (Box 1, Folder 40.0031)
    - Lou Bunin, NYC, June 3, 1986. (Box 1, Folder 40.0032)